<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="about_title">About this module</string>
    <string name="about_description">
        Although It is incorrect to detect specific app installation, yet not every app using root provides random packagename support. In this case, detected apps that use root (such as Fake Location and Storage Isolation) is equal to detected root itself.\n\nAt the same time, some smart apps use various loopholes to acquire your applist, so that it can draw a persona for you.\n\nThis module provides some methods to test whether you have already hidden your applist nicely. Also, it can work as an Xposed module to hide some apps or reject applist requests to protect your privacy.
    </string>
    <string name="about_how_to_use_title">How to use this module</string>
    <string name="about_how_to_use_description_1">
        #Do I need riru extension#\nRun a detection test directly. If the file detections column is all N, then your ROM has already intercepted this kind of detections, and there is no need to install the riru extension. Otherwise, you need the riru extension to intercept file detections. Note: the riru extension is unstable, which may or may not be limited to causing problems such as card startup and flashbacks. Please judge whether it is necessary.
    </string>
    <string name="about_how_to_use_description_2">
        #How to enable hide#\nFirst create a template in Manage Templates, then apply the template in Select Effective Apps. You should and ONLY should check System Framework in Xposed module scope/whitelist.
    </string>
    <string name="about_how_to_use_description_3">
        #How to confirm whether hide is successful#\nApply a template to the module itself, then activate Hook Self in settings and start detection test.
    </string>
    <string name="about_how_to_use_description_4">
        #Is template modification effective in real time#\nExcept for file interceptions, yes. To update file interception policy, you need to force stop and restart target apps.
    </string>
    <string name="about_hook_differences_title">Differences among hook methods</string>
    <string name="about_hook_differences_description">
        Normal apps use some of API requests to acquire applist, but bad apps will use other methods (loopholes) to detect it. Attention, under global mode (Reject applist requests) if hide Intent query there may be some problems with share, start browser, etc.
    </string>
    <string name="about_developer">Developer</string>
    <string name="about_support">Support and feedback</string>
    <string name="about_open_source">Open source licenses</string>
</resources>