<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="about_title">About this module</string>
    <string name="about_description">
        Although It is incorrect to detect specific app installation, yet not every app using root provides random packagename support. In this case, detected apps that use root (such as Fake Location and Storage Isolation) is equal to detected root itself.\n\nAt the same time, some smart apps use various loopholes to acquire your applist, so that it can draw a persona for you.\n\nThis module provides some methods to test whether you have already hidden your applist nicely. Also, it can work as an Xposed module to hide some apps or reject applist requests to protect your privacy.
    </string>
    <string name="about_how_to_use_title">How to use this module</string>
    <string name="about_how_to_use_description_1">
        #Do I need magisk extension#\nIf you need file detection / maps scan interceptions, you need install the magisk extension.\n\nAttention, the magisk extension is a Riru module, which requires Riru v25/26.
    </string>
    <string name="about_how_to_use_description_2">
        #How to enable hide#\nYou can create templates in \"Manage Templates\". Then apply the templates in \"Select Effective Apps\". (You can also select extra apps for targets.) You should and ONLY should check \"System Framework\" in Xposed module scope / whitelist.
    </string>
    <string name="about_how_to_use_description_3">
        #Is template modification effective in real time#\nExcept for file interception and maps scan, yes. To update file interception policy, you need to force stop and restart target apps.
    </string>
    <string name="about_hook_differences_title">Differences among hook methods</string>
    <string name="about_hook_differences_description">
        Normal apps use some of API requests to acquire applist, but bad apps will use other methods (loopholes) to detect it.\n\nFor maps scan, if you enable an Xposed module for an app, then the app can search /proc/self/maps to find the module. In the blacklist mode, the maps information of the apps in the list will be automatically hidden, but in the whitelist mode you need configure manually.
    </string>
    <string name="about_developer">Developer</string>
    <string name="about_support">Support and feedback</string>
    <string name="about_open_source">Open source licenses</string>
</resources>